jardello.eu 2016-05-08

# .::AS::. Jardello - Auto Surf : Free Auto Hits Traffic Your WebSites

What personally identifiable information is collected on this site?  
Visitors may supply personally identifiable information (such as name, e-mail address) for various purposes on this site. These purposes include receive e-mail newsletters or simply asking a question about .::AS::.Jardello. .::AS::.Jardello does not collect personal information from you unless you are a member. This means that you can visit our site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. 

Security  
Personally identifiable information is stored on our Web server and is not publicly accessible. Further, personally identifiable information is only accessed by SurfJardello employees on a need to know basis. All .::AS::.Jardello employees must go through privacy training upon starting with .::AS::.Jardello. 

E-mail  
All e-mail lists maintained by .::AS::.Jardello contain the names of people who have requested to be a member of SurfJardello. The e-mail address collected by .::AS::.Jardello will never be rented to outside firms for any purposes. 

What anonymous information is collected on this site? Anonymous information is collected for every visitor to this site. This includes login count, date and time, IP numbers and browser type. 

How is it used?  
The anonymous information is used by ASJardello to find cheaters. 

How does this site use cookies? .::AS::.Jardello uses cookies to identify you when you log in. This cookies contains only the entered login information (e-mail address and password). 

View for credits  
.::AS::.Jardello do show other Web sites when you view for credits. Please note that when you are viewing for credits, you are entering another site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours. 

Links  
.::AS::.Jardello may contain links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours. 

E-mail Links  
We use e-mail links located on this site to allow you to contact us directly via e-mail. We use the information provided in your e-mail to respond to your questions or comments. We may also store your comments for future reference. Your personal information is not shared with third parties. 

Legal Disclaimer  
We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to confirm to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on .::AS::.Jardello. 

For more information  
If you have any questions, concerns or comments, please e-mail admin@jardello.com
